Hey Jake, congratulations. Welcome to
Tampa. Uh just kind of walk us through
the process. Obviously, you have, excuse
me, lots of uh of opportunities in
different places, but what was it about
about Tampa um that that you really like
this opportunity here?
Uh yeah, I think uh going back to
probably end of January, uh talking with
my agent, kind of listed out some places
that I wanted to be and uh kind of had
this one, you know, towards the top, if
not the top. Um you know, obviously
they've been able to win a lot of games
here over the last few years, uh the
recent Super Bowl. Uh always been a fan
of Baker Mayfield from afar. uh don't
know him well, but you know, he's always
kind of somebody who I uh I watched most
of his throws and uh most of his plays
and uh yeah, hard to beat Tampa as far
as just living too. So, I'm excited to
be a part of it, uh, the organization
here. And, uh, yeah,
>> we talked to Kate Oddton, I guess, who
you played with briefly, of course, at
UDub, and he said I think he's got a
little bit of Baker Mayfield in him,
maybe approaches it a little bit
different way, but do you see that same
kind of gamer on on Sunday, Monday,
Thursday?
>> Uh, yeah. I mean, I think it's somewhat
similar. um you know, neither one of us
are are huge guys with a a huge arm, but
um able to process quickly and stuff
like that. But um
>> yeah,
>> you know, I think also I I I'm excited
to be in the room and kind of see how he
operates
>> and uh and handles himself because I
think that's kind of the
>> the main deciding factor on how a lot of
these things go. So uh yeah. All right.
>> Thanks. Mhm.
>> Our next question will come from Greg
Almond.
>> Hey Jake, obviously you know you're a
backup quarterback. The whole thing is
kind of being prepared to come in and uh
you had a stent uh three years ago and
you had a stent this year. Just want to
ask you why you didn't think things went
as well this time around and how you get
back to kind of the win in football you
had the first time you stepped in uh for
Joe there in Cincinnati. Yeah, I think
the uh the preparation side of things I
think I I got a good process on and um
you know kind of going back even to uh
multiple years on on practice squad
preparing and and with the idea being
that at some point you know going to get
that opportunity and obviously in 2023
we did um were able to get hot there for
a little bit and uh and you know I think
you look at 2025 obviously didn't go as
well um you know I don't think that was
like a lack of preparation lack of
effort
But uh you know I think whenever you
don't play well in a small sample you
know you got to look at the film and say
okay what what was the the role that I
played in that and uh and assess some of
those things and you know I look back on
2025 you know we we're kind of going
through a tough spot as a team and and I
tried to step in and play some hero ball
a little bit and you know we we were
struggling running the ball we're were
struggling on a lot of different areas
and I thought oh okay I'm going to you
know I I played did well in 2023 and
after not playing for two years, I'm
going to be the one to like save us. And
so you end up forcing some throws that
were dumb. Um and you know trying trying
to do too much which is is uh big big uh
no no for quarterbacks. So um you know I
think after you kind of have your own
personal takeaways then you know you
don't let it shake your confidence or
anything like that. I still think I'm a
really good quarterback in this league
and um excited to get a fresh start and
uh you know learn the offense here and
and get back to uh playing some winning
football
>> Jake. Thanks. Welcome to Tampa.
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> Next question will come from Scott
Reynolds. If any media have questions,
please raise your hand.
>> Hey Jake, just wanted to get your
thoughts as a quarterback. you're coming
to a team that arguably might have the
best offensive line in football and then
the receiving core with guys even though
they lost Mike Evans but Chris Godwincha
Ibuka Jaylen McMillan I'm sure you you
know from watching Washington and uh Tez
Johnson and you know and others what are
your thoughts on the weapons that are in
place here and then the offensive line
that u that this team has assembled
>> yeah um well I ran into Tristan Warf in
the weight room and the strength coach
said that that's what offensive
lineman's supposed to look like and and
I would agree. Um he was wearing a tank
top that I didn't they didn't hand hand
me the same I think it was about this
wide. I was like I had my little I had
my little welcome package and they
didn't put one of those in there for me.
I was kind of confused why not. And uh
but yeah, I mean I we didn't have a ton
of uh crossover with Tampa. Um, so I
haven't watched a ton of them, but I
felt like every time the highlights
would turn on, it was, you know, a
different receiver making a big play,
which obviously starts with uh with
Baker, you know, being able to keep
everything, you know, stay explosive
with a bunch of injuries uh last year.
And so, you know, I know in my time in
the NFL, whenever there's some injuries
that happen, some guys get a chance to
to step up, and it seems like a lot of
the younger guys around here did. Um, so
you know, you go to the next year after
everybody getting some of that
experience and you're hoping that that
pays dividends in the following year,
too. So, um, yeah, excited to be a part
of the offense here. Obviously, I got a
new offensive coordinator, so excited to
learn that system. And, uh, you know,
outside of that, I I I was in the AFC
North. We didn't we weren't we didn't
see a ton of the NFC South uh, crossover
game, so I haven't really been able to
watch it. And then lastly, when when it
comes to Zack Robinson, what what
attracted you to Tampa Bay in terms of a
scheme fit, have you had any
conversations with Zack and how your
skill set might align with with what
they want to do here in Tampa?
>> Yeah, I mean, I think for me, like the
skill set, the offense should be catered
to the starter, which is obviously
Baker, and I think my skill set is
similar to that. So, I think anytime
you're in a backup situation, you're
you're kind of looking for that. Um, you
know, there's there's exceptions to
that, but uh, you know, going and
playing behind Lamar Jackson and they
build the offense for Lamar Jackson,
it's not it's not not going to look the
same for for me if I was a backup there.
So, here I feel like they don't really
need to change a bunch of stuff. Um, you
know, if if it were a situation where I
was I was playing um, got similar skill
set. Obviously, Baker's played a lot
more football than me and at a very very
high level. Um, but yeah, as far as as
Zach, uh, just heard good things as far
as, uh, guys that played for him
personalitywise, you know, I think the
the scheme kind of morphs into whatever
you need it to be. Um, Zack Taylor was
obviously in uh, LA with Shawn McVey. So
was Zach Robinson. So, kind of hoping
there's some carryover in in the
verbiage and all that, but um, you know,
I think when you're making decisions on
where you're going to go, you want to
you want to play for good people. and uh
heard nothing but good things about the
coaches here.
>> Thank you, Jake. Welcome.
>> Thanks,
>> Jenna Lane.
>> Managing the the dynamic in the
quarterback room is is very important
and often does fall on the backup
quarterback. What What are some things
that that you uh can uniquely bring to
this room?
>> Uh I mean, I haven't been in the room
yet, so I I'm not exactly sure. I
haven't really met any of the other
quarterbacks. So, you know, I think
that's
>> but that's kind of probably where the
backup role comes in is having some
emotional intelligence on on where
you're needed. Um, I think the main
thing that I try to do as backup is just
be really prepared and not care that
anybody knows if I'm prepared or not.
So, you know, it's like the guy that
that knows the answer to the question
that he's asking. Like try not to be
that guy and just try to be supportive
on um, you know, things that come up.
And obviously coming here I got u you
know no real crossover with any of the
coaches here. And so I got a completely
different background and different
experiences that you know try to be
helpful and um especially when you go
play these AFC North opponents. I've
been in the division for for five years
and so try to be helpful there and you
know had some good years uh been a part
of some good offenses and so things that
worked, things that didn't work. um you
know how we did certain things there
maybe things that I I thought you know
we do better here just different
experiences um and offenses and but at
the end of the day is trying to trying
to be helpful try to provide some value
and uh and be prepared for whatever
situation comes up
>> and you kind of answered a little bit of
it already but like in Cincinnati in
particular like what what were you able
to kind of bring to the to the room
there? Yeah, I think the I think the
best backups uh you know they
I always get asked that and it's like
well
Joe Burrow was good in Cincinnati
because Joe Burrow is good and I think
if you're the backup they start trying
to take credit for stuff like that then
you know that starts to get pretty
annoying. Um, but I think just being
consistent and uh being pretty even
keel, you know, I know for some of the
games I've started, it was nice if, you
know, the other backup quarterback for
me at the time was just somebody that
was kind of just levelheaded like, "All
right, here's what they're doing." You
know, here's, "Hey, good throw here."
Because it can get really emotional.
Everybody can get all emotionally
charged. And so, you know, I think I do
a good job of just being a calm presence
when everyone else is is freaking out.
And so, uh, yeah, I think that's kind of
where I I've hung my hat and, um, in
Cincinnati, but I think it really just
comes down to having the experience of
of being in those shoes a lot.
>> And that's that's certainly a skill.
>> Yeah.
>> Being calm in in situations. Not
everyone can do that.
>> Yeah. I mean, I think no, nobody wants
to hear the backup quarterback who's not
playing, you know, complain about
something. It's like, all right, just
be relaxed. try to be helpful and focus
on trying to help everybody win.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, that's all we have time for.
Thank you very much, Jake.
>> Yep. Thanks, guys.